<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Michael P. Heinl</title>
    <link>https://heinl.net/authors/michael/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Michael P. Heinl</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#39;https://heinl.net/impressum&#39;&gt;Impressum/Legal Notice&lt;/a&gt; &amp;middot; &amp;copy; {year} Michael P. Heinl</copyright>
    
	    <atom:link href="https://heinl.net/authors/michael/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://heinl.net/authors/michael/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heinl.net/authors/michael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p style=&#39;text-align: justify;&#39;&gt;I&#39;m a security researcher with the Fraunhofer Institute for Applied and Integrated Security AISEC and a doctoral candidate of Technical University of Munich&#39;s Chair of IT&amp;nbsp;Security. I am regularly involved in teaching both at TUM and as lecturer for digital security at Heilbronn University of Applied Sciences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#39;text-align: justify;&#39;&gt;My research interests are generally in the area of security and trustworthiness of critical systems and processes, such as the ICT supply chain (particularly in industrial environments) or remote voting technologies, as well as deriving corresponding implications for economy, society, and policy. Due to its holistic approach as well as regular collaborations with researchers from different application domains, my research is inherently multidisciplinary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p style=&#39;text-align: justify;&#39;&gt;Before joining Fraunhofer AISEC, I have gained extensive international experience in both industry and academia while studying and conducting research in the United States, Israel, Ireland, Estonia, and Germany as well as working in the security divisions of IBM and Japanese telecommunications giant NTT. Prior to that, I worked several years in the German automotive supplier industry where I also successfully underwent a dual professional training as information technology officer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
